Guide to the J. Walter Thompson Company. Newsletter Collection, 1910-2005 RL.00733
David M. Rubenstein Rare Book & Manuscript Library
J. Walter Thompson Company. Newsletter collection
1910-2005
David M. Rubenstein Rare Book & Manuscript Library
J. Walter Thompson Company
RL.00733
17 Linear Feet
0.14 Gigabytes
The J. Walter Thompson Company (JWT), founded in 1864, is one of the largest enduring advertising agencies in the U.S. The Newsletter Collection comprises the agency's internally produced newsletters, which date from 1916 through 2005. Newsletters survive from the main office, certain domestic and international offices (particularly from Atlanta, Chicago, Detroit, London, Los Angeles, New York and San Francisco), and divisions and affiliates (especially Brouillard Communications; Lord, Geller, Federico, Einstein; Dialog; and Thompson Recruitment Advertising) of JWT. Topics contained in the newsletters include staff biographical information; office events; account and client news; featured campaigns; marketing; merchandising; consumer behavior; research and planning; developments and issues in television, radio, and print media; and personal activities of the staff. Most of the newsletters are in English, but German, Spanish, French, Italian and Portuguese language publications are also present. As the Company continues to publish house organs, the collection will continue to grow.
Online Items
Selected newsletters from this collection have been digitized and are available in the J. Walter Thompson Newsletters - Duke Digital Collections.
Access Restrictions
Rare originals are closed to researchers. Please consult use copies as indicated in the Scope and Contents Note.
Materials less than 15 years old are closed to non-JWT users.
Provenance
The J. Walter Thompson Company. Newsletter Collection was received by the David M. Rubenstein Rare Book & Manuscript Library as a transfer in 1987.
Collection Overview
The J. Walter Thompson Company (JWT) Newsletter Collection comprises the advertising agency's internally produced newsletters, which date from 1916 through 2005. Included are newsletters from the main office, certain domestic and international offices (particularly from Atlanta, Chicago, Detroit, London, Los Angeles, New York and San Francisco), and divisions and affiliates of JWT (especially Brouillard Communications; Lord, Geller, Federico, Einstein; and Thompson Recruitment Advertising). The newsletters document JWT's business over the years by providing a forum for JWT staff worldwide to report on their activities and on developments in the advertising industry. Topics include staff biographical information; office events; account and client news; featured campaigns; marketing; merchandising; consumer behavior; research and planning; developments and issues in television, radio, and print media; and personal activities of the staff. In addition, the newsletters reflect many aspects of the corporate culture that set the tone of life in JWT offices. They report events such as blood drives, baseball games, office parties, staff retreats, and more. The sense of civic duty that JWT tried to instill in its personnel by encouraging its staff members to volunteer in their communities runs through many of the newsletters, particularly in the 1950s and 1960s, often concurrent with the agency's Ad Council and public service work.
The physical form of the newsletters evolved from several stapled, typewritten pages in the 1910s and early 1920s, to a (usually) four-page typeset newsletter in the 1950s, to a short newsprint magazine in the 1970s, to a longer glossy magazine in the 1980s. In the 1990s, some newsletters switched to a fully electronic format. The entries for each newsletter in this inventory detail the frequency of publication of the newsletters, the availability of indexes, irregularities in volume numbering and dating, and other pertinent information. Most of the newsletters are in English, but German, Spanish, French, Italian and Portuguese language publications are also present. Publications will be added to the collection as the archives receives and processes newsletter additions.
The collection is arranged into three series and four indexes: Main Newsletters, Domestic Newsletters, and International Newsletters; and an Alphabetical List of Newsletter Titles, an Alphabetical List By Client of Campaign of the Week Articles, News Bulletin Contents by Author, and News Bulletin Contents by Title.
The Main Newsletters Series holds the primary house organ for the company and includes some market research results as well as the opening of many international offices in 1929 and 1930. Newsletter articles includes account news, client lists--or account gains and losses--and biographies and short notes on JWT staff, including professional accomplishments, promotions and transfers, visits to other JWT offices, and personal events (i.e. marriages, births, and deaths).
The Domestic Newsletters Series is divided into three subseries--Offices, Divisions, and Other Newsletters. The Offices Subseries documents activities in the major JWT offices in the U.S.--Atlanta, Chicago, Detroit, Los Angeles, New York, and San Francisco. The office newsletters reported account gains and losses, campaign updates, and other business news, with substantial coverage of local events such as staff promotions and transfers, wedding and birth announcements, office parties, anniversaries, company-related sports events, personal and social news. They also updated local staff on news from elsewhere in the agency. Many of these publications were issued regularly as supplements to the main company newsletter published in New York; for instance, the New York News, at some points during the 1960s, was printed on the back page of the J. Walter Thompson Company News. The Divisions Subseries includes newsletters from subsidiaries and corporate divisions such as Brouillard Communications (JWT division for corporate advertising and public relations), Dialog (JWT division for public relations), Lord, Geller, Federico, Einstein (JWT affiliate for premium advertising), and Thompson Recruitment Advertising (previously named World Wide Agency, the JWT division for employee recruitment advertising). The newsletters report client gains and losses of the division and its individual offices, staff transfers and promotions, marriage and birth announcements, and other personal and social news. Some newsletters primarily address issues and developments pertaining to the specific aspect of advertising with which the division/affiliate concerns itself. The Other Newsletters Subseries includes publications that deal with advertising issues beyond a specific office's activities, along with newsletters issued by the Information Centers of the New York and Chicago offices that described their holdings or abstracted articles from newspapers and magazines relating to advertising. The newsletters address a broad range of issues relating to the advertising industry--marketing; merchandising; research; planning; consumer behavior; client news; major staff changes for agency executives from JWT offices worldwide; reports on single accounts or industries; and reports from the television, radio, print, and other media.
Newsletters from JWT offices in Canada, Latin America, Europe, Asia/Pacific, and Africa are found in the International Series. Most of these newsletters report the business of the offices and of the agency as a whole, noting account gains and losses, campaign results, market surveys, and other developments. News of office parties and anniversaries, employee transfers and promotions, staff birthdays and marriages, visits from JWT executives from other offices, and other social and cultural news are often included in the newsletters; for some newsletters, such lighter news comprises the bulk of the information published. A few newsletters cover much more specific marketing topics, such as Food and Drink News from London and JWT Media Information from Australia.
Conditions Governing Access note
Restrictions to access: Materials less than 15 years old are closed to non-JWT users. Where an item has been removed from containers and relocated, a dummy folder has been placed at the item's logical location within the container list, with the title enclosed by brackets and its physical location noted.
Conditions Governing Access
Collection contains electronic records that must be requested through the collection guide and accessed in our reading room. Contact Research Services with questions.
Alphabetical Listing of Newsletter Titles
40 Something Box RN2 (RESTRICTED)
402 Lex Box OV2
60 Seconds Box DO14
A Régua T, Box IN2
Advertising Bulletin Box IN5
Advertising Business Box IN5
Alector Box IN4
Apcunoticias Box IN2
Aquí Latinoamerica Box IN2
Australian News Box IN11
Belgian Bulletin Box IN3
Bitácora Box RN2 (RESTRICTED)
Boletim JWT Box IN2
Bolétin del Centro de Informaciones de JWTA, Box IN2
Bolétin J.W.T.A. Box IN2
Book Bulletin Box IN5
Book News Boxes IN5-IN6
Business Communications Box ROV1 (RESTRICTED)
Case for Advertising Box IN6
Change in the Marketplace Box DO14
Change Box RN1 (RESTRICTED)
Client Tell Box DO12
Commodore Box RN2 (RESTRICTED)
Commodore's Log Box IN1
Common Market Newsletter Box IN3
Communications Watch Box DO12
Consumer Affairs Boxes IN6-IN7
Consumer Briefs Box DO14
Consumer Response Box DO2
Contents List Box IN7
Dal mondo del Mezzi/From the World of Media, Box IN4
Detroit Ad-Vocate Box DO5
Detroit Thompson Times Box DO5
Dialog Among Us Box DO12
Earthquaking News Box DO11
Electronic Media Update Box DO14
Entre nosotros: bolétin informativo interno, Box IN2
European Food News Box IN7
European Managers Monthly Digest Box IN3
Extracts Box IN7
Family Square Box IN7
Finger-Tip Facts on File Box DO8
Flagship Box DO8
FOB Detroit Box DO5
Fog Talk Box DO12
Foghorn Box DO12
Food and Drink News Box IN7
Food for Thought Box DO15
Food News Box IN7
Food Service News Box DO15
Ford/Thompson Times Box RN1 (RESTRICTED)
General Interest Box IN7
HTA Today Boxes IN11, RN3 (RESTRICTED)
In the News Box RN2 (RESTRICTED)
Indian File Box IN11
Indonesia Letter Box IN11
Industry News Digest Box DO15
Information Center Flash Box DO2
Information Center Box DO8
Informations JWT Box IN3
Informations JWT Paris Box IN3
Inside News Box DO12
Inside NYO Box DO8
Intercomm Box IN11
International Market News Box IN7
Issue Box IN8
J. Walter Log Box DO15
J. Walter Thompson Co. News Bulletin Box MN9
J. Walter Thompson Company New York News, Box DO8
J. Walter Thompson Company News (Canada), Box IN1
J. Walter Thompson Company News (main newsletter) Boxes MN9-MN15
J. Walter Thompson Company News (Netherlands), Box IN4
J. Walter Thompson Company News (San Francisco) Box DO11
J. Walter Thompson Kid Stuff Box RN2 (RESTRICTED)
J. Walter Thompson News Box MN16
J. Walter Thompson World Box RN2 (RESTRICTED)
J. Walter Thompson Worldwide Update Box DO15
J. Walter Trumpet Box DO7
J. Walter World Box DO15
J.W.Trends Box RN2 (RESTRICTED)
Junior News Box DO8
JWT (Spain) Box OV3
JWT Aktuell Box IN3
JWT/BMRB News Box IN8
JWT Bulletin Box IN8
JWT Campaign News Box DO15
JWT Circle Box IN11
JWT Club Bulletin Box IN11
JWT Communique Box IN11
JWT Company World Box DO16
JWT Detroiter Box DO5
JWT Directions Box DO5
JWT Friday Box DO9
JWT Front and Center Box OV2
JWT Greenwatch Box RN2 (RESTRICTED)
JWT in Print Box RN2 (RESTRICTED)
JWT Information Services Box IN8
JWT Library Flash Box DO2
JWT Market Reports Box IN8
JWT Marketing News Box IN8
JWT Media Bulletin (Europe) Box IN11
JWT Media Bulletin (Germany) Box IN11
JWT Media Information Box IN11
JWT Merchandising Newsletter Box IN8
JWT Mittwoch Report Box IN3
JWT News Boxes MN9, MN16-MN19, OV1
JWT News (Australia) Box IN11
JWT Newsgram Box IN11
JWT Newsletter (Philippines) Box IN11
JWT Report Frankfurt Box IN3
JWT Times Box DO7
JWT Weekly News Box MN9
JWT World Highlights Box DO16
JWTimes Box RN1 (RESTRICTED)
JWTNews Box MN16
JWT-Report Box OV3
Keep in Touch Box DO9
Key Response Box RN3 (RESTRICTED)
Letter from the Chairman Box DO12
Letzter Blick auf 1983 Box IN3
LGFE Newsletter Box DO12
Listener Box ROV1 (RESTRICTED)
Live Wire Box RN1 (RESTRICTED)
Llegando Box IN2
Lo que pasa en JWT Chilena Box IN2
Looking Ahead Box IN11
Madcap Melodies Box DO11
Mahlzeit Box IN3
Mail Call Box DO5
Management News Summary Box DO17
Market Facts Box IN11
Matter of Fact Box DO17
Media Newsletter Box RN2 (RESTRICTED)
Media Report Boxes DO18-DO20
Media Update Box RN3 (RESTRICTED)
Meet-In Box IN4
Merchandising News Box DO20
Michigan Avenews Box DO3
Monthly Happenings Box DO1
Move Memos Box DO20
Netherlands Newsletter Box IN4
New Products and Sales Promotions in Europe, Box IN8
New Products Box IN8
New Products Bulletin Box DO20
New York News Box DO9
New York Thompson Boxes DO9, OV2
News Bulletin Boxes MN2-MN5
News Flash Box DO9
News from J. Walter Thompson Detroit Boxes DO5, RN1 (RESTRICTED)
News Letter (South Africa) Box IN11
Newsletter (Hong Kong) Box IN11
Newsletter (Indonesia) Box IN11
Newsletter J. Walter Thompson Chicago Box DO3
Newsletter (main series) Boxes MN6-MN8
Notícias de medios Box IN4
Notícias Box IN4
Notícias JWT Box IN2
Notiziario JWT Italia Box IN4
Now Read This: The Newsletter of PTM Thompson Advertising Box IN11
OK! Box IN1
Once Over Lightly Box DO20
Out of the Blue Box ROV2 (RESTRICTED)
Owl and the Lamp Box RN1 (RESTRICTED)
People Box DO10
Pressespiegel Box IN4
Previews Box DO10
Print Capsules Box DO20
Profit-Sharing Plan News Box DO20
Project 466 Box DO10
Promotion Box OV3
PTM Thompson Box IN11
Qué Hay de Nuevo en JWT Mexico Box IN2
Qué pasa en Atlas Box IN2
Qué pasa en JWT AmericaLatina Box IN2
Qué Pasa en JWT Perú Box IN2
Qué pasa en JWT Venezuela Box IN2
Qui...Thompson Box IN4
Round the Square Boxes IN8-IN10
Sales Promo Update Box DO3
Sales Promotion Box IN10
Sales Promotion & New Products in Great Britain Box IN10
Scrip Box IN10
Service Newsletter Box DO10
Skilled Techniques in Guiding Group Action, Box DO20
Spezialausgaube Sport Box OV3
Talker Box RN1 (RESTRICTED)
Talker Online Box RN1 (RESTRICTED)
Target Box RN1 (RESTRICTED)
Temas Thompson Box IN2
This Week in Detroit Box DO6
This Week--Info Centre Box IN11
Thompson Times Box DO7
Thompson Today Box DO13
Thompson Way Boxes RN3, ROV1 (RESTRICTED)
Thompsonline Box DO13
Tokyo JWT News Box IN11
Trends Box IN10
Tudo Bem na JWT Brasil Box IN2
Vantage Box RN2 (RESTRICTED)
Vienna Report Box IN3
Viewpoint Box RN3 (RESTRICTED)
Weekly News Digest Box DO4
Westwords Box DO4
Whistling Sausage Box RN3 (RESTRICTED)
White Papers Boxes DO20, RN2 (RESTRICTED)
Who is New? Box IN4
World News Roundup Box RN2 (RESTRICTED)
Alphabetical Listing By Client of Campaign of the Week Articles
Articles may be found in the main company newsletters under its various titles, in Boxes MN9-MN12.
Absorbine Jr.: 1947 Feb. 17
Action Gemeinsinn (JWT volunteer work--Frankfurt): 1962 Feb. 7
Alexander Smith Inc.: 1952 Mar. 24
Alexander Smith Inc.: Carpet: 1952 Dec. 29
Alexander Smith Inc.: Innerspring weave: 1954 Mar. 1
Alexander Smith Inc.: Sloane-Blabon: 1952 Apr.14
Alpargatas (Merito shoes--Buenos Aires): 1950 May 22
Aluminum Limited: 1954 July 5; 1955 Aug. 15; 1958 Nov.10; 1960 Apr.27.
Aluminum Limited: Home remodeling: 1959 Oct. 14
American Dairy Association/Aunt Jemima (June Dairy Month): 1957 June 10
American Gas & Electric Co.: 1954 Mar. 22
American Petroleum Institute: 1961 July 5
American Red Cross: 1960 Mar. 2
American Red Cross: Disaster Year: 1958 Jan. 13
American Red Cross: Fund drive: 1959 Mar. 4
American Trucking Industry: 1952 Sept. 22
American Weekly: 1946 Oct. 28; 1948 Feb. 9; 1949 Jan. 24.
Ansell Rubber Co.: 1954 Oct. 11
Anthracite Institute: 1948 May 17; 1948 Nov.8; 1950 Sept. 11; 1951 June 18.
Appliance Corporation of America (Washing machine): 1947 Apr.21
Aquascutum Co. Ltd. (Expedition coat): 1955 Aug. 29
Arnold Schwinn: 1948 Nov.15
Association of American Playing Card Manufacturers: 1950 May 8; 1954 Sept. 20.
Association of American Playing Card Manufacturers: Bridge handbook: 1961 July 19
Association of American Playing Card Manufacturers: Congress, Bicycle: 1955 Oct. 24
Association of American Playing Card Manufacturers: Solitaire set: 1955 Nov.14
Atlantic Refining Co. (Rio de Janeiro): 1952 Dec. 1
Atlantis Sales Corp. (French's mustard): 1948 Nov.1; 1957 Apr.29.
Ballantine: 1946 Nov.18; 1947 Sept. 29; 1948 Apr.5; 1951 Aug. 13; 1952 July 14; 1953 Mar. 23.
Ballantine: 3-Ring campaign: 1953 Oct. 12
Ballantine: Foreign Intrigue: 1953 Aug. 24
Bank of Nova Scotia:
Bank of Nova Scotia: Personal security--Toronto: 1954 June 7
Bank of Nova Scotia: Public relations--Toronto: 1951 Nov.12
Barrett Co., Ltd. (Building supplies--Montreal): 1956 Apr.23
Beech-Nut (Baby food): 1970 Feb. 6
Better Homes & Gardens: 1957 Aug. 26
Blue Chip Stamp Co. (Billboard): 1961 Nov.1
Blue Cross/Blue Shield: 1954 Apr.5; 1954 Nov.1; 1956 July 30; 1961 May 24.
Blue Cross/Blue Shield: Hospital, medical services: 1951 Nov.19
Blue Cross/Blue Shield: Michigan hospital/medical services: 1957 Mar. 25
Blue Cross/Blue Shield: Senior health: 1961 Oct. 11
Borg Warner (Norge): 1953 Apr.27; 1947 Dec. 15; 1951 Apr.9.
Bowman Dairy: 1947 Mar. 3; 1948 Dec. 20.
Bowman Dairy: Kiddie Parks: 1957 May 20
Boyle-Midway (Sweepstakes): 1960 Mar. 30
Brillo Manufacturing: 1946 Oct. 7; 1950 Feb. 20; 1957 Jan. 14.
Brillo Manufacturing: Soap pad with detergent: 1961 Apr.12
Brillo Manufacturing: Soapier: 1960 Oct. 19
British Industrial Plastics (Would It Be Better?campaign--London): 1961 Aug. 23
Buitoni Foods (New client): 1955 Sept. 5
Burlington Industries (Color campaign): 1955 Dec. 5
Burroughs: 1951 Apr.16; 1956 Mar. 19.
Buxton: 1946 Dec. 2; 1948 Dec. 6; 1949 Nov.14; 1950 May 15.
Cafes de Mexico (Saboro--Mexico City): 1957 Sept. 23
California Lima Bean Advisory Board: 1953 Jan. 12
California Olive Advisory Board: 1951 Mar. 5
California Raisin Advisory Board: 1953 Sept. 28; 1956 Nov.12.
California Raisin Advisory Board: Public relations: 1961 Feb. 8
California Wine Advisory Board: 1946 Sept. 23; 1947 Sept. 15; 1949 Feb. 7; 1949 Oct. 10; 1950 May 1; 1950 Oct. 9; 1951 Sept. 17; 1953 Oct. 26.
California Wine Advisory Board: California Wine Show: 1953 Mar. 9
California Wine Advisory Board: Wine Discovery Month: 1952 Oct. 13
Caterpillar Tractor Co. (International): 1949 Dec. 5
Caupolican Chiguayante (Textiles--Santiago): 1954 Feb. 22
Champion Spark Plug Co.: 1956 Aug. 20; 1958 Jan. 6; 1957 Feb. 11; 1960 Nov.23.
Champion Spark Plug Co.: Aviation: 1957 Sept. 16
Champion Spark Plug Co.: Leadership campaign: 1960 Feb. 17
Cheese Bureau--London: 1955 Dec. 26
Chesebrough-Pond's: 1970 Feb. 20
Chesebrough-Pond's: Angel Face: 1946 Sept. 30; 1950 Oct. 2; 1962 July 5; 1953 Sept. 14.
Chesebrough-Pond's: Beauty Around the World: 1959 Dec. 9
Chesebrough-Pond's: Cold cream: 1958 Nov. 3; 1960 Aug. 24.
Chesebrough-Pond's: Dry Skin cream: 1959 Aug. 26
Chesebrough-Pond's: Glamour in Paris: 1957 Dec. 9; 1958 Nov.17.
Chesebrough-Pond's: New cold cream: 1958 Jan. 20
Chesebrough-Pond's: Paris a la Mode: 1960 Feb. 24
Chesebrough-Pond's: Pond's history: 1959 July 15
Chesebrough-Pond's: Pond's Lips: 1954 May 24
Chesebrough-Pond's: Reader's Digest article: 1960 Nov.2
Chesebrough-Pond's: Sweepstakes: 1959 Sept. 23
Chesebrough-Pond's: Vanishing cream: 1947 June 9
Christmas (Seasonal campaigns): 1947 Dec. 22
Chun King Sales, Inc.: 1956 Sept. 10
Chun King Sales, Inc.: Jeno's Italian food: 1958 Mar. 31
Chun King Sales, Inc.: Oriental foods: 1954 Sept. 27
Church & Dwight: 1953 July 20
Church & Dwight: Baking soda: 1956 June 25
Church & Dwight: Baking soda/first aid: 1957 June 24
Columbia Mills, Inc. (Venetian blinds): 1951 Apr.23
Compania Chilena Electricidad--Santiago: 1952 Aug. 25
Continental Airlines: 1960 Feb. 3
Continental Airlines: Caesar campaign: 1959 Jan. 7
Continental Airlines: International: 1961 Mar. 29
Continental Airlines: New client: 1958 May 26
Credit Union National Association: 1953 May 25
Credit Union National Association: Historic Scenes campaign: 1955 July 4
Crompton-Richmond (Textiles): 1957 July 22
Crusade for Freedom (Anti-Communist advertisements): 1956 Dec. 31
Cuna Mutual Insurance Society: 1952 Mar. 31
David Whitehead Limited (Fabrics--London): 1954 Jan. 4
Devoe & Raynolds Co.: 1950 June 5; 1952 Mar. 10; 1951 Jan. 22; 1955 Aug. 22.
Douglas Aircraft Co.: 1947 Aug. 11; 1948 May 3; 1949 Jan. 3; 1950 July 17; 1951 Feb. 26; 1952 Apr.28; 1958 Dec. 10.
Douglas Aircraft Co.: 3-part program: 1953 Feb. 23
Douglas Aircraft Co.: DC-7: 1954 Dec. 27
Douglas Aircraft Co.: DC-8: 1957 Mar. 18; 1955 Nov.28; 1958 June 16.
Douglas Aircraft Co.: Luxury Interiors: 1959 Aug. 5
Douglas Aircraft Co.: Military: 1957 Apr.8
Douglas Aircraft Co.: Space Age equipment: 1961 Feb. 1; 1961 May 31.
Dr. West's:
Dr. West's: Flexite: 1952 Feb. 11
Dr. West's: Toothbrushes: 1959 Apr.1
E. Gomme Ltd. (Furniture--London): 1954 Apr.26; 1961 Jan. 11.
E.J. Brach: 1949 Mar. 21
E.R. Squibb & Sons: 1952 Feb. 25
Eastman Kodak: 1947 Mar. 24; 1949 May 16; 1949 Nov.7; 1956 Mar. 26; 1960 Apr.27.
Eastman Kodak: Better Living campaign: 1961 Aug. 16
Eastman Kodak: Bombay: 1953 June 22
Eastman Kodak: Celebrity campaign: 1959 June 17
Eastman Kodak: Disney/Annette Funicello: 1962 Feb. 7
Eastman Kodak: Functional advertising: 1948 Apr.12
Eastman Kodak: Functional concept: 1947 June 23
Eastman Kodak: Give and Take campaign: 1959 Dec. 16
Eastman Kodak: International: 1946 Oct. 21
Eastman Kodak: Kodacolor film: 1958 June 2
Eastman Kodak: Kodapak sheet: 1953 Aug. 17
Eastman Kodak: Norby television series: 1955 Jan. 3
Eastman Kodak: Old-Fashioned Christmas: 1960 Dec. 21
Eastman Kodak: Open Me First: 1957 Nov.18; 1958 Nov.24; 1960 Dec. 7; 1961 Dec. 20.
Eastman Kodak: Recordak: 1950 May 29
Eastman Kodak: Slide shows: 1961 Oct. 4
Eastman Kodak: Teenage advertising: 1950 Aug. 21
Eastman Kodak: Turn Around campaign: 1961 Apr.19
Eastman Kodak: Youth campaign: 1953 Apr.6
Eastman Kodak/Disney World of Color: 1961 Sept. 6
Elgin National Watch Co.: 1947 July 21; 1948 Oct. 4; 1950 Dec. 11; 1950 Mar. 13; 1956 Sept. 24.
Elgin National Watch Co.: Year Old Boy campaign: 1959 Feb. 11
Employers Mutual of Wausau: 1956 Dec. 3
Employers Mutual of Wausau: Tribute by Wisconsin: 1955 Apr.18
Employers Mutual of Wausau: Workman's Comp: 1953 Dec. 28
Esso S.A. Petro. Argentina (Insecticides--Buenos Aires): 1952 Dec. 22
Farrell Steamship Lines:
Farrell Steamship Lines: Johannesburg: 1949 July 11
Farrell Steamship Lines: New York: 1954 July 26
Fibracel (Hardboard lumber--Mexico City): 1951 June 4
Fieldcrest Mills, Inc. (Bed/Bath One Look): 1957 Mar. 11
Firestone S.A. (Safety campaign--Sao Paulo): 1954 June 14
Firestone Tire Co.(New inFrance campaign): 1961 Nov.1
Florida Citrus Commission: 1950 Nov.13; 1951 Aug. 6; 1953 Nov.23; 1954 June 21.
Florida Citrus Commission: Grapefruit: 1951 Oct. 29
Ford and Sylvania (Promotional contest): 1959 Jan. 21
Ford Motor Co.: 1946 Dec. 9; 1949 Jan. 10; 1950 Jan. 9; 1950 Mar. 27; 1952 Feb. 4; 1953 May 4; 1954 Jan. 11; 1956 June 18; 1956 May 14; 1956 Oct. 8; 1957; 1958; 1959; 1960; 1962
Ford Motor Co.: 1949 models: 1948 May 24; 1948 June 14.
Ford Motor Co.: 1950 models: 1949 Nov. 21
Ford Motor Co.: 1951 models: 1950 Nov. 27
Ford Motor Co.: 1953 models: 1952 Dec. 15
Ford Motor Co.: 1954 best selling car: 1955 Mar. 14
Ford Motor Co.: 1955 models: 1954 Nov. 15
Ford Motor Co.: 1958 Thunderbird: 1958 Feb. 3
Ford Motor Co.: 1959 Thunderbird: 1959 Feb. 4
Ford Motor Co.: 300,011 Trucks Sold: 1962 Jan. 31
Ford Motor Co.: 36 page advertisement: 1959 Apr. 29
Ford Motor Co.: 5 Firsts: 1959 Oct. 7
Ford Motor Co.: 600 Truck Models: 1960 Nov. 30
Ford Motor Co.: Anglia: 1960 July 6
Ford Motor Co.: Animated television commercials: 1960 June 15
Ford Motor Co.: Award-Winning Style: 1958 Oct. 13
Ford Motor Co.: Deal with CBS: 1955 June 13
Ford Motor Co.: Dealer advertising: 1947 Sept. 1
Ford Motor Co.: Dealer Advertising Funds: 1951 June 25
Ford Motor Co.: Dealers "car safety": 1949 Aug. 29